In the name of Jesus Christ.
Listen, every influence....
You are being influenced to do what you don't want to do.
You are being influenced to say what you don't want to say.
You are being influenced to look at what you don't want to look at.
You are being influenced to think what you don't want to think.
Right now, I command every influence out...in the name of Jesus.
out...in the name of Jesus.
Out!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Demon Speaking: Idol, spirutal husband
Yes from the mother side. From the fathers side.
I have frustrated her.
I have made her run to foreign men with 8 children, and all of them run away.
She has no home, I have frustrated her...
as she can see her self now
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Hallelujah!
Let me speak to your heart;
I want to speak to your heart.
Any temple in your heart.
Any temple in your spirit.
Every will that is not Gods will...within your spirit and your heart.
I command them out in the name of Jesus.
I say out...in the name of Jesus.
I say, I command them out! I say out!!!
Manifestation of evil spirits.
She's mine. I am the spiritual husband, the man in charge.
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
I am strong.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Be delivered!
I say be delivered!
Testimony Time
My name is Angela Uchechi. I am 38 years old.
I am from Eboni, Nigeria
The problems that has brought me here
was: a spiritual husband, evil attacks
and severe headaches. It has affected me in so many ways.
I was always angry. I was never happy.
But I pretended to people around me that I was happy.
I use to eat and make love in the dream.
I was barren for 11 years, until I prayed with the man of God on Emmanuel TV/
After the prayer, I met with my husband,
and I conceived my baby.
During the course of todays Mass Prayer Service, we saw you manifest. What happened to you?
When the man of God was praying,
I didn't know what came over me.
I felt a cold sensation, and I found myself on the floor
I was delivered.
Hallelujah, so do you believe that this deliverance you received has brought breakthrough
and salvation to your life?
Women: Yes, I believe. In Jesus name I believe.
To me and my family, in Jesus name.
We want to encourage you to make this deliverance permanent...
and make God's word a standard for your life, in Jesus mighty name.
Amen.
Thank you Jesus I am delivered.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to witness more of Gods power at work in our generation today
and stay up to date with the latest: prophecies, deliverances, service, and and testimonies
from the SCOAN, Emmanuel TV
changing lives, changing nations and hanging the world.